<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iqbalzetto.com</title>
    <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Iqbalzetto.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iqbalzetto.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Me and Myself 2 - Bad Idea</title>
      <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/posts/mnm-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iqbalzetto.com/posts/mnm-2/</guid>
      <description>Kemarin saya menulis untuk membuat satu tulisan setiap harinya. Bahwa saya akan sediakan satu jam untuk menulis. Mungkin itu sebenarnya bukan ide yang bagus, bahkan di hari pertama ini saya langsung berfikiran begitu. Karena timeframe satu jam pasti akan membuat saya bingung apa yg mesti saya tulis.
Itu hal yang saya pikirkan sebelum saya membuka aplikasi editor dan mulai mengetik. &amp;ldquo;Mulai aja dulu&amp;rdquo;, tagline tokopedia itu memang luar biasa. Mungkin kebiasaan saya untuk selalu kebanyakan mikir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me and Myself 1 - Tentang menulis</title>
      <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/posts/mnm-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iqbalzetto.com/posts/mnm-1/</guid>
      <description>Sudah lama sekali Saya tidak merenung sambil menulis. Sebuah sensasi bagai berdialog dengan diri sendiri. Ketika jari mengetik, pikiran mengeja, terkadang berhenti sejenak, tarik nafas, ulangi.
Sesi Me and Myself ini adalah sesi dialog dengan diri sendiri membahas apapun yang saya pikirkan saat menulis.
Topik sesi MnM pertama ini adalah tentang menulis itu sendiri. Mungkin hanya salam pembuka dan motivasi untuk menulis
Kenapa saya perlu menulis?
Karena somehow menulis membuat Saya berfikir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iqbalzetto.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I am a programmer, I make web related stuff
I like music, sometimes I take my guitar and sing wonderwall, or creep or whatever song that is not complicated I can only jreng jreng and sing, and I&#39;m happy with that.
I also like to read fantasies stuff, manga or light novel. Sometimes I want to write my own somehow.
This web is my first time playing with Hugo and I am not well versed in markdown format, but I am quite excited to see what I can do with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iqbalzetto.com/experience/</guid>
      <description>This page is still under construction. Anyway, here&#39;s my portfolio in pdf format</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/fantasies/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iqbalzetto.com/fantasies/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&#39;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://iqbalzetto.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iqbalzetto.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&#39;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>